Hello, welcome to Teen Swadesh. You are
watching our
special show Mid-Cap Masala on mid-cap stocks. I am with you
Abhishek Satya Vratam. There is a pressure environment in the market today again.
You
will see a slowdown in Nifty, there is a weakness of around 25 points.
But there is buying in Nifty Bank today
because NBFCs have received a big relief from RBI.
Due to this, we are seeing
that among the banking stocks, there is
buying in financial stocks today and the
leadership is coming from there. But there is a
huge fall in wire and cable stocks today because
UltraTech has announced to enter this segment. So, there
is pressure on UltraTech shares as well because the company is going into a new segment,
that too with very less capital. We will have to
see what kind of news comes out from there in the future.
But for now, we have seen
that all the Byron Cable shares have become KE1
or Havells and Poly
Cab. You will see all these shares trading with a huge fall today.
Poly is
now down at 16 and in KE1 shares,
we are seeing that it is around 19.  There
is pressure on all these stocks. We will discuss further
and also try to understand what
your strategy should be in the market. Is the
one-sided decline that was going on in the market around 22500, is there any
sign of stopping? We will take expert views on this
and also understand the best trades for you in the midcap.
But first, let us
bring three pictures through which we will
explain to you what is the mega action in midcaps today
and which side is
seeing more trades in the market today.
Three pictures on your screen.
Prestige is down around 4%. The
reason for this decline is that there are
reports that the
Income Tax Department is investigating the company's office.
Due to this, the stock is seeing a decline. There is
pressure on Titagarh Rail.
Morgan Staley has reduced the target and the stock is
trading around 4% below. The
target has been reduced from 00 to 90.
Due to this, we are seeing pressure in the stock.
However, there is a buying trend in SRF. The
stock is up at 2%. AB Capital says
that the demand for specialty chemicals is strong.
While there is a rise being seen there,
most of the shares are down. If
you see today in midcap, the advance decline ratio is
very bad. Around 2200 shares
are weak and in comparison to that, only 425 shares are
trading strongly. So this
is the picture of the market, but let us
understand the trade for you in the index because today
is the monthly expiry, today the February series will
expire. What trade should you
take, what strategy should be there, what
rollovers should be done, what deals should not be done, let us
understand this and will bring a 3-
hour
trade of Nifty and today to guide you in the market and to
tell you the earning strategy,
Amol Aath Wale of Kotak Securities has joined us. Thank you very much
for giving your time. Welcome to Amol on 9th.
Today Nifty is in a tight range. The only relief we
can say is that 22500 has not been broken, it is still there.
Please tell me whether
any trade is being made in the index. For the next three hours,
Nifty or Nifty Bank
looks better to you. Hello and good
afternoon. I think today if we
Specifically, if we look at the intraday momentum,
I feel that it has moved away from a range.
Perhaps some momentum may increase in the last wave,
but I think it should be
seen conditionally. If any major resistance or
support is broken, then perhaps such a
structure is showing that after that
we can see a slight increase in the momentum. I think for the bulls
or for the traders, on the higher side, the
first one will be 22600. If that level is broken, then there are
chances of further increase in the momentum on the positive side or a short term recovery.
Currently, it is visible on the charts.
Second, if we look at the higher side,
22450 is
quite promising,
but if that is broken, then I think
we can see further increase in the momentum on the selling side. Currently, the view
is neutral, but the focus will definitely be on the range breakout.
This view on Nifty has been done
from the level of 22500, but Amol, please
tell me, if anyone wants to buy stocks  If you want to
take a trade, where have you focused? Is it a mid-cap
stock or a large-cap stock?
You have one large-cap and one mid-
cap. I think I'm looking at stocks that are
quite promising.
If we look at 70, after a major correction, the
stock has seen a slight improvement today.
If we look at it level-wise, it
is coming out quite promising [sangeet] and its stop-loss will be
220. If we look at the overall FMCG stocks, they are
moving in a slightly different pattern. The
market is falling so much, but for the last two-three days,
we are seeing a slight increase in buying activity in all the FMCG stocks. If
we look at Nestle,
after a correction, the stock has consistently
maintained a higher-higher loss formation.
If this setup continues, then
from a positional point of view, the bullish setup that has formed in Nestle is
likely to continue. Looking at the charts, it is
okay. It is advisable to buy Nestle as well.  There
is a slight tilt towards buying in the consumer market and
whenever there seems to be a crisis situation in the market,
people
create consumer positions. Nestle is doing well
today and there is a rally of around half,
but Amol's target is 2365, exactly ₹1 above from here
and the stop loss is
₹20 from Amol's side and the second stock
is ICI General Insurance i.e. ICI
Lombard, the target will be 00 and the
stop loss for this is 210, so
both the stocks are on the bullish side,
these two stocks are in Amol's list, okay
Amol, please tell me that
today we saw an initial rally in Bandhan Bank and RBL,
but now the rally in Bandhan stock is almost left, it is hardly
around one and a half, it is at the low
level of the day and when we were discussing in the morning, it was
expected that RBI has
reduced the risk weight on micro finance loans, so Bandhan  And RBL will also be
its beneficiary. What do you think, should there be
any rally on the chart here
or should we avoid it? It would be better to adopt a
wait and watch approach in Bandhan.
But on the flip side, the
formation of RBL Bank is quite
promising.
Somewhere or the other, it is converting into a sell-off.
Whenever it reverses, the
correction is quite sharp. So the
price cuts that are coming are quite sharp. I
think a little base should be formed in it.
At least a range should open. A
range, if we can say, if we
look at Bandhan Mang, there is a resistance level of 146-48 on the higher side.
On the flip side,
if we look, there is
a support around 132-130. Consolidation there
may be seen in the stock in the coming days.
But on the other hand, if we
look at RBL Bank, RBL Bank is
stuck in a consistent range. If we
look at the higher side also, a positive
consolidation is visible. If we look at the
daily charts,  If we look at this, a higher bottom
formation has formed.
If RBL Bank continues this formation at that level, then
I think a positional point
for this RBL Bank can definitely be looked at.
Supports will be at 158, where a
reversal occurred after the last correction. On the
higher side, 175 will be the first resistance,
and if that is crossed, then
we can see this stock moving towards 178-180 somewhere. It is
in a range, and the
divergence is clearly visible. Nifty is slightly
down, but today we are seeing a
rise of around 250 points in Nifty Bank, it is
above 1, but the overall
texture of the market is slightly on the weaker side
because the advance decline ratio is very
weak, and the market will remain a bit dull
because from the wick below 14, we are
seeing weakness around 2 today, so this
dullness is clearly visible. Today we are seeing
weakness in auto shares, and energy shares are
also facing some pressure today.
We are seeing a decline in BPCL and OGC today,
but the major
damage and the major accidents are
definitely there. The decline in wire and cable
stocks like KEI has gone beyond 21,
so there has been a major wealth road.
We will bring research on this
soon, but first let's understand
where you will make money in options. We will
bring the champion of options
[music].
Sachin Gupta of Five Paisa Capital is
with us. Sachin ji, thank you very much for your time.
Tell us what to trade in options.
Where are the opportunities according to you.
Very good. Afternoon and
if we focus on options in today's trading session, then
my view is that
if we look at this particular stock on Varun Beverages Limited,
a bearish formation is seen forming on the daily charts. The
breakdown of the bearish flank pattern is seen getting confirmed here. So, what is the idea of
buying a put option of 450 in Varun Beverages Limited?  It would be advisable to place
a stop loss of ₹16 in the March series, whose premium is currently hovering around ₹20,
and
a target of ₹16 on the upside can be placed. The
maximum loss here will be ₹3500.
If we look at the maximum profit, then
around ₹7000
is expected. Varun Beverages
is already down around ₹6, and Sachin feels that
this stock can fall further. So, you are
advised to buy a put option through options. A ₹
450 put will be available at a price of ₹0. The target will be ₹
28. You have to proceed with a stop loss.
Maximum profit of ₹1, maximum loss of ₹7000,
straight payout of ₹0, so the risk and reward ratio is 1:2.
Sachin, thank you very much for
your time and for sharing this excellent
strategy with our viewers.
Now let us learn about a stock for investment
through Mid Cap's Maharathi and Mid Cap.  Marathi shares, that is,
a champion stock of investment,
Nirav Bora of Gem Financial is with us to tell you,
Nirav ji, thank you very much. Tell us
which midcap is on your radar and where to invest.
Hello Abhishek ji, hello to all the viewers. So,
if we talk about the midcap space, then first of all,
before telling the stocks, I would like to
tell you that in the last one or
two months, we have seen a very good decline
in midcaps because valuation wise, the
levels had gone up quite high,
especially in small caps. Now, if we
talk about quarter three, then
in midcaps also, many of the results were very low as compared
to large cap space, so
we have seen a good correction. If we
look at it on an average, then we have seen a good
correction of 30-35. Now we feel
that valuation wise,
many stocks have reached a very good level and my
today's pick will be Voltas. So,
if we talk about Voltas, if we talk about quarter three, then
first of all, the numbers of Voltas have
come out quite good.  There are two main
segments from where its revenue comes.
One is UCP which is
known as Unitary Cooling Products and the
other is EP that is Electro Mechanical
Project and Services which
works in high industries. So these are the two biggest
segments of Voltas and the performance of both was
quite good.
If I talk about revenue in quarter three, then we
saw an increase of 18% on YOY basis. We have earned revenue of Rs 3100 crore
for Voltas in the third
quarter which was very good. If I
talk about UCP segment, then we
saw revenue increase by 20% on YOY basis. We have
also seen a YOY growth of 21% on EMPF. So
all in all, we feel that the
EMPC quota is very strong, the order
book is very strong for Voltas and
if we look ahead, the
summer season will
start and it is a seasonal stock, every
summer we see that
this stock takes a good run, in fact if we
talk about today  If we talk about it,
it is trading at around 1300-1305 level, which is 52 week high or if we
talk about all time high, then it was
around 1950, its all time high level, from
where we have seen a good
correction of around 32, now the reason for this was
that F Ice is selling its goods and where the
valuations were a little high, we have
seen a good selling, so having said that
we are choosing and looking at those stocks
where we feel that
one or two quarters can be very good in the future,
so Voltas is our pick because
we feel that when the summer
season starts, the demand for AC coolers will
increase significantly, so
in the last quarter also, if point taken, point taken, yes
Nero Bhai, Nero Bhai, you understood it completely,
we will interrupt you, I apologize for this, there is a
little shortage of time, but see,
from the price point as well as from the sentiment point,
both things are working
for Voltas and I  By looking at Nirav's body
language I can understand that it is okay,
he must have checked the fundamentals
but the increasing heat in Mumbai is
also the effect of this that Voltas is coming out of their coffers,
well thank you very much Nirav
for giving your time and this excellent stock had gone to the
range of Rs. 00,000 for our viewers, it has fallen from there and has
come down, so it is
good from the valuation point of view as well and the atmosphere is about to
become hot now, it is February but the
temperature has become very high in Mumbai,
well I will end this show here, Nirav
ji, thank you very much and
thank you very much for giving your time and for
discussing all the stocks, a small